Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 1707 Records WAG.298
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series II: General Administrative and Locals Files, 1950-2006
  - AFSCME: Convention, 1978; cuid6304 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - AFSCME: Convention, 1980; cuid6305 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - AFSCME: Convention, 2000; cuid6306 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - AFSCME: Financial, 1975-1997; cuid6307 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - AFSCME: Organizing Convention, Sep 2001; cuid6308 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - AFSCME: Reports, Newsletters, 1993-1998; cuid6309 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - AFSCME: "Stopping Sexual Harassment", Undated; cuid6310 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Benefits Booklets, [1965], 1994; cuid6311 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Clerical Staff, 1994-2002; cuid6312 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Administrative Binder, A-E, 1976-1977; cuid6313 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Administrative Binder, F-Z, 1976-1977; cuid6314 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Clippings, Flyers, Ephemera, 1996, undated; cuid6315 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Correspondence, Memoranda, 1991-2000; cuid6316 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Events, 1991-1997; cuid6317 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Events--African-American History Month Celebration, 1996; cuid6318 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: General Administrative, 1986-2000; cuid6319 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU) Committee: Meeting Minutes, 1991-1999; cuid6320 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Constitution, circa 1996, 1997; cuid6321 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Constitutional Amendments, 2001; cuid6322 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Constitutional Convention, Local 1707: Minutes, May 1958; cuid6323 (Box 46, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence, 1993-2000; cuid6324 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence: Memoranda, 1997-2002; cuid6325 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence: Memoranda, Flyers, 1997-1998; cuid6326 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence: Memoranda, Flyers, 1999; cuid6327 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Feb - Apr 1999; cuid6328 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, May 1999; cuid6329 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jun 1999; cuid6330 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Jul 1999; cuid6331 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Aug 1999; cuid6332 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Sep 1999; cuid6333 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Oct 1999; cuid6334 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Nov 1999; cuid6335 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Correspondence: Outgoing, Dec 1999; cuid6336 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Delegate Assembly: List, [2003]; cuid6337 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - Delegate Assembly: Memoranda, 1981-2000; cuid6338 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Directors' Reports, 2001; cuid6339 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - District Council 1707: General, 1991-1998; cuid6340 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - Education Department/Education, 1988-2000; cuid6341 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Education Department: Memoranda, Flyers, 1998-2000; cuid6342 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - Election Committee Meeting: Minutes, Mar 1992; cuid6343 (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - Election Material, 1992-1998, undated; cuid6344 (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 10, 1992, cuid6345 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 24, 1992, cuid6346 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 25, 1992 (I), cuid6347 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 25, 1992 (II), cuid6348 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Election Objection: AFSCME Election Department--Hearing Transcript, Jun 25, 1992 (III), cuid6349 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Employee Leave Requests, 2004; cuid6350 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Executive Board: Constitutional Admendments, 1986-1988; cuid6351 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Executive Board: Correspondence, 1996-1997; cuid6352 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Executive Board: Correspondence, 1998-2000; cuid6353 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Executive Board: Correspondence, 2001; cuid6354 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Executive Board: Member List, 2001; cuid6355 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Executive Board: Memoranda, 1997-2001; cuid6356 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Family and Medical Leave Act, Undated; cuid6357 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Field Services Department: Reports, 2005; cuid6358 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Finance Committee, 1999-2000; cuid6359 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Financial Records: Acting Fiscal Affairs Director Memos, 2002; cuid6360 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Financial Records: ADAPT Northwest (South Africa), 2001; cuid6361 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Financial Records: AFL-CIO, 2001; cuid6362 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Financial Records: AFSCME, 2000-2001; cuid6363 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Financial Records: American Arbitration Association, 2002; cuid6364 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Financial Records: American Red Cross of Greater New York, 2001; cuid6365 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Financial Records: Association for the Help of Retarded Children, 2001; cuid6366 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Financial Records: Audit, 1987; cuid6367 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Financial Records: Black Women's Leadership Conference, 2001; cuid6368 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Financial Records: Board of Directors Presentation, 2004; cuid6369 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Financial Records: Bolton-St. John's Inc., 2001; cuid6370 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Financial Records: The Chief-Leader, 2001; cuid6371 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Financial Records: Children and Families for Green (Political Action), 2001; cuid6372 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Financial Records: Chinese-American Planning Council, 2001; cuid6373 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Financial Records: Coalition of Black Trade Unionists (CBTU), 2001; cuid6374 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Financial Records: Contingencies, 1999-2001; cuid6375 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Financial Records: Correspondence, 1997-2001; cuid6376 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Health and Insurance Fund, 2001; cuid6377 (Box 9, Folder 33)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Professional Staff Employees Retirement Fund, 1983-1986; cuid6378 (Box 9, Folder 34)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Professional Staff Employees Retirement Fund, 1987-1989; cuid6379 (Box 9, Folder 35)
  - Financial Records: DC 1707 Professional Staff Employees Retirement Fund, 1990-1993; cuid6380 (Box 9, Folder 36)
  - Financial Records: Financial Meeting--Nov 30, 2000, 1999-2000; cuid6381 (Box 9, Folder 37)
  - Financial Records: General, 1974-1997; cuid6382 (Box 9, Folder 38)
  - Financial Records: Investment, 1998; cuid6383 (Box 9, Folder 39)
  - Financial Records: Notes, Ephemera, 1997, undated; cuid6384 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Financial Records: Pride at Work Convention, 2001; cuid6385 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Financial Records: Rent Negotiations, 1997; cuid6386 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1973-1982; cuid6387 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1983-1986; cuid6388 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1987-1988; cuid6389 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1989; cuid6390 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1990; cuid6391 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1991-1992; cuid6392 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 1993-1994; cuid6393 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Financial Records: Reports--Accountant's Assembly, 1994; cuid6394 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Financial Records: Reports (Income Statements), 1996-1999; cuid6395 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Financial Records: Reports--Budget Comparisons/Projections, 1997-1998; cuid6396 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Financial Records: Reports (Income Statements), 2000-2001; cuid6397 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 2001-2002; cuid6398 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Financial Records: Reports, 2003-2005; cuid6399 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Financial Records: Staff Employees Retirement Plan, 1999; cuid6400 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Financial Records: Statements, 1996; cuid6401 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Freedom of Information Act (FOIA) Requests, 1997; cuid6402 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - General Membership Meetings, 1964-1973; cuid6403 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Government and Civic Employees Organizing Committee, 1950; cuid6404 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Health and Safety Committee, 1995-1996; cuid6405 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - International Foundation of Employee Benefit Plans: Conference, 1998; cuid6406 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Labor: General, 1997; cuid6407 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Latino Affairs Committee, 1985-1992, undated; cuid6408 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Legal: Leibowitz and Mars LLP, 1998-2000; cuid6409 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Legal: Sipser, Weinstock, Harper and Dorn, 1995; cuid6410 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Long Term Disability Certificate, 1998; cuid6411 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Monthly Reports, Jan - Apr 1998; cuid6412 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Monthly Reports, 2001; cuid6413 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - New York State Reports, 1996-1997; cuid6414 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Not-for-Profits/Non-Profits Report, 1998; cuid6415 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Notes, 1996, undated; cuid6416 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Office and Professional Employees International Union (OPEIU), 1997, 2000; cuid6417 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Office Renovations, 1993; cuid6418 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Organizing, 1985, 1995-1996; cuid6419 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Organizing, 1997; cuid6420 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Organizing, 1999-2000; cuid6421 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Political Action Committee, 1992-1997; cuid6422 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Political Action Committee, 1998-2000, undated; cuid6423 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Political Action Conference, 1994, undated; cuid6424 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Press Releases, 1993; cuid6425 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Professional Staff/Professional Employees Union, 2000; cuid6426 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Public Employees Organized to Promote Legislative Equality (PEOPLE) Committee, 1995-2000; cuid6427 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Rallies and Demonstrations, 1995; cuid6428 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Shop Assignment Visits, 1992-1993; cuid6429 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Shop Assignment Visits, 1993; cuid6430 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Shop Assignment Visits, 1993; cuid6431 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Social Service Employees Union (SSEU), Local 371, 1994; cuid6432 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Staff Meeting, Apr - May 1993; cuid6433 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Staff Meetings: Assistant Directors, 1987-1989, 1998; cuid6434 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Staff Meetings: Minutes, 1963-1964; cuid6435 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Staff Telephone Extensions, [1998]; cuid6436 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Weekly Schedules, 1997-2000; cuid6437 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Women's Affairs Committee, 1997-2000; cuid6438 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Local 95: General Administrative, 1989-1996; cuid6439 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Local 95: Executive Board Meeting, Unidentified Meeting, 1997-1998; cuid6440 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund, 1996; cuid6441 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meetings, 1996; cuid6442 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Feb 12, 1997; cuid6443 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--[Trustee Board Meeting?], [Sep 1997]; cuid6444 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Feb 5, 1998; cuid6445 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting (I), Nov 17, 1998; cuid6446 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting (II), Nov 17, 1998; cuid6447 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Mar 10, 1999; cuid6448 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, May 27, 1999; cuid6449 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Nov 17, 1999; cuid6450 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, Feb 16, 2000; cuid6451 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Local 95: Head Start Employees Welfare Fund--Trustee Board Meeting, May 4, 2000; cuid6452 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Local 107: Correspondence, 1997; cuid6453 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Local 205: Agencies, 1978-1981; cuid6454 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Local 205: AFSCME, 1984; cuid6455 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Local 205: AFSCME--PEOPLE Fund Raising Campaign Kit, 1978; cuid6456 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Local 205: Arbitration, 1998; cuid6457 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Local 205: Awards Dinner/Dance, 2001, undated; cuid6458 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Local 205: Board and Committee Members, 1978-1979; cuid6459 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Local 205: Communication Committee, 1979-1982; cuid6460 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Local 205: Communication Committee Meetings, 1978-1979; cuid6461 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Local 205: Correspondence, Memoranda, 1978-1981; cuid6462 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund, 1986-1990; cuid6463 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund, 1989-1991; cuid6464 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (I), 1990-1992; cuid6465 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (II), 1990-1992; cuid6466 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (I), 1992-1993; cuid6467 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund (II), 1992-1993; cuid6468 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council Local 205--Welfare Fund/Group Legal Fund, 1998; cuid6469 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council of New York--Bargaining, 1970-1988; cuid6470 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Local 205: Day Care Council of New York--Job Descriptions, 1972; cuid6471 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Local 205: DC 1707 Constitution, 2002; cuid6472 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Local 205: Elections, 1999; cuid6473 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Local 205: Elections for Delegates to AFSCME International Conventions, 1978-1980; cuid6474 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Local 205: Ephemera, 1979-1984, undated; cuid6475 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Local 205: Event Programs, 1986-1987; cuid6476 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Local 205: Executive Board Meetings, 1977-1991; cuid6477 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Local 205: Financial Documents, 1978-1983, 2002; cuid6478 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Local 205: Flyers, Handouts, 1979-1996, undated; cuid6479 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Local 205: General Membership Meetings, 1980-1983; cuid6480 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Sep 1997-Jan 1998; cuid6481 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Feb-Mar 1998; cuid6482 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Apr-Jun 1998; cuid6483 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Local 205: Grievances, Jul-Dec 1998; cuid6484 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Local 205: Legislation, 1974-1980; cuid6485 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Local 205: Legislation (I), 1974-1984; cuid6486 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Local 205: Legislation (II), 1974-1984; cuid6487 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Local 205: Legislation, [1983]-1986; cuid6488 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Local 205: Legislative Committee, 1977-1979; cuid6489 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Local 205: Legislative Committee--Correspondence, 1979-1982; cuid6490 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Local 205: Legislative Committee--Meetings, 1976-1982; cuid6491 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Local 205: Meeting Minutes--Alvin Turner File, 1984-1985; cuid6492 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Local 205: Meetings--Other, 1978-1980; cuid6493 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Local 205: Members, Undated; cuid6494 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Local 205: Negotiating Session(s), 1980, undated; cuid6495 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Local 205: New York City Day Care Direct Lease Program Report, 1976; cuid6496 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Local 205: New York City Government, 1984, undated; cuid6497 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Local 205: New York State Worksite Child Care Centers--Boards of Directors, 1994; cuid6498 (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - Local 205: Programs, 1980-1984; cuid6499 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Local 205: Public Employees Organized to Promote Legislative Equality (PEOPLE), Undated; cuid6500 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Local 205: Shop Stewards Meetings, 1979-1983; cuid6501 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Local 215: AFSCME, 1974, 1997-1998; cuid6502 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Local 215: AFSCME, 1999-2000; cuid6503 (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Local 215: AFSCME, 1999-2000, undated; cuid6504 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Local 215: Agencies, 1994-1998; cuid6505 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Agency/Shop Steward Listing, 1996; cuid6506 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Local 215: Agencies--AFSCME Dues Reporting Forms, 1997, undated; cuid6507 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining, 1981-1994; cuid6508 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining, 1991-1999; cuid6509 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--Federation Group Work Agencies, 1985-1995; cuid6510 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--Jewish Board of Family and Children's Services/Jewish Child Care Association, 1985-2000; cuid6511 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--New York Association for New Americans, 1991-2000; cuid6512 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Bargaining--United Jewish Federation of MetroWest, [1993]-2000; cuid6513 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Correspondence, 1997; cuid6514 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Local 215: Agencies--Staff Representatives Reports, 1993-2000, undated; cuid6515 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Local 215: Arthur Tate Case--Misappropriation of Funds, 1996-1997; cuid6516 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Local 215: Board Meeting Material, [Jun, Dec 1999]; cuid6517 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Local 215: Correspondence, 1985-2000; cuid6518 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Local 215: DC 1707, 1993-2000; cuid6519 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Local 215: Election Materials, 1996; cuid6520 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Local 215: Ephemera, Undated; cuid6521 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Local 215: Financial Records, 1979-2000; cuid6522 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Local 215: General Administrative, 1994-2000; cuid6523 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Local 215: Grievances/Grievance Committee, 1985-2000; cuid6524 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Local 215: Judicial Panel and New York State Supreme Court Cases (Internal Disputes), 1992; cuid6525 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Local 215: Leadership Training Program, 1981, 1986; cuid6526 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Local 215: [Leadership Training], 1997; cuid6527 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Local 215: Leadership Training Program--Shop Stewards, 1995; cuid6528 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Local 215: Local 215 Executive Board, 1998-2000; cuid6529 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Local 215: Meetings/Workshops/Events, 1995-2000; cuid6530 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Local 215: Membership Meetings, 1993-1999, undated; cuid6531 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - Local 215: New York City Central Labor Council, 1999-2000; cuid6532 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - Local 215: New York Labor Party/Labor Party, 1997-1999, undated; cuid6533 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Local 215: New York State Reports, 1997; cuid6534 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Local 215: Notes, 2000, undated; cuid6535 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Local 215: Petition to DC 1707 for More Staff Representatives, 1994; cuid6536 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Local 215: Retreats, 1995-1999; cuid6537 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Local 215: Steward Manuals/Training, 1974-1993; cuid6538 (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Local 253: Agencies--Correspondence, 1997-998; cuid6539 (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Local 253: Bargaining, 1997-1998; cuid6540 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Local 253: Correspondence--Elections, 1998-2000; cuid6541 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Local 253: Correspondence--General, 1996-2000; cuid6542 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Local 253: Grievances, 1995-2000; cuid6543 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Local 253: Meetings--Notices, 1996-1999; cuid6544 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Local 253: Miriam E. Aguayo Statement, 1998; cuid6545 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Local 389: Agencies--Contracts, Contact List, 1998-2003; cuid6546 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Local 389: Agencies--Correspondence, Memoranda, 1980-2000; cuid6547 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Local 389: Constitution, 1981-2004; cuid6548 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Local 389: Contacts--Board of Estimate, Human Resources Administration (HRA), Undated; cuid6549 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Local 389: Correspondence, 1978-2004; cuid6550 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Local 389: Correspondence--Memoranda, Flyers, 1978-1999; cuid6551 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Local 389: Correspondence--Memoranda, Flyers, 2000-2005, undated; cuid6552 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Local 389: Education, 1989, undated; cuid6553 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Local 389: Election Materials, 1995-1998; cuid6554 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Local 389: Ephemera, 1996-2002; cuid6555 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Local 389: Executive Board Meetings, 1998-2002; cuid6556 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Local 389: Executive Board Meetings, 2003-2005; cuid6557 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Local 389: Financial Records, 2002-2004; cuid6558 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Local 389: Financial Records--Health and Welfare Fund, 2002-2003; cuid6559 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Local 389: Grievances/Grievance Forms, 1990-2003; cuid6560 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1988-1990; cuid6561 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1990; cuid6562 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1990-1991; cuid6563 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Health and Welfare Fund--Trustees Meetings, Reports, 1991; cuid6564 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Pension and Health and Welfare Funds--Trustees Meeting, Jul 31, 2002; cuid6565 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Pension and Health and Welfare Funds--Trustees Meeting, Consultant's Report, 2003; cuid6566 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Local 389: Home Care Employees Pension and Health and Welfare Funds--Trustees Meeting, Correspondence, 2004; cuid6567 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Local 389: Home Care Registry Bill, 1989-1990; cuid6568 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Local 389: Home Care Work Group, 1990-1991; cuid6569 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Local 389: Home Care Workers Report, 1991; cuid6570 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Local 389: Human Resources Administration (HRA)--Hearing on Home Care Services Program and Protective Services for Adults, 1990; cuid6571 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Local 389: International Foundation--Annual Employee Benefits Conference of Employee Benefit Plans, 2005; cuid6572 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Local 389: International Foundation of Employee Benefits Plans--Fraud Prevention Institute, 2000; cuid6573 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Local 389: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA)--Conferences/Conventions, 2004-2006; cuid6574 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Local 389: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA)--NYC Central Chapter, 1998-1999; cuid6575 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Local 389: Labor Council for Latin American Advancement (LCLAA)--NYC Central Chapter, 2004-2005; cuid6576 (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Local 389: Leadership Conference, 1990; cuid6577 (Box 16, Folder 7)
  - Local 389: Life Insurance Fund, 2002-2004, undated; cuid6578 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - Local 389: Living Wage Bill--New York City, 1987, 2001-2003, undated; cuid6579 (Box 16, Folder 9)